A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Personal, United States Commission on Industrial Relations (Walsh Commission), Series Z.12 FA1162
Rockefeller Archive Center
Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Personal, United States Commission on Industrial Relations (Walsh Commission), Series Z.12
1914-1915
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commission on Industrial Relations
Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (John Davison)
Rockefeller, John D. (John Davison)
FA1162
1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box.
Scope and Contents
Contains testimony of JDR Jr., JDR Sr. and others.
Conditions Governing Access
Open is research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Arrangement
As received.
- Testimony of JDR Jr. given before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations, New York City (January 25 and 26, 1915) and Washington, D.C. (May 20, 21, 22, 1915), 3 copies. (Box 1)
- Statement of JDR Jr., 1915 January 25 and 26; 10 copies. (Box 1)
- Statement of JDR Jr., 1915 May 20-21; 3 copies. (Box 1)
- Testimony of JDR Jr. in connection with Industrial Matters, given before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations, 1915 January 25-26 (Box 1)
- Testimony of JDR Jr. in connection with Rockefeller Foundation, given before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations, 1915 January 26-27 (Box 1)
- Information furnished by the Rockefeller Foundation in response to Questionnaires, 1915 (Box 1)
- Testimony of JDR Sr. given before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations, New York City, 1915 February 5 (Box 1)
- Testimony of L. M. Bowers, Washington, D.C., 1915 May 24 (Box 1)
- Testimony of Dr. Charles W. Eliot, New York City, 1915 January 29 (Box 1)
- Testimony of Jerome Greene, 1915 February 2-3 (Box 1)
- Testimony of A. Barton Hepburn, New York City, 1915 February 4 (Box 1)
- Testimony of W. L. Mackenzie King, Washington, D.C., 1915 May 24-25 (Box 1)
- Testimony of Dr. George W. Kirchwey, 1915 February 4 (Box 1)
- Testimony of Ivy Lee, New York City (January 27-28, 1915), Washington, D.C. (May 22-23, 1915) (Box 1)
- Testimony of E. H. Weitzel, Denver, Colorado, 1914 December 8-9 (Box 1)
- Testimony of J. F. Welborn, Denver, Colorado, 1914 December 4-7 (Box 1)
- Letters Supplied (Box 1)
- Final Report of the Commission on Industrial Relations, 1915 (Box 1)
- "Industrial Unrest", by John A. Fitch ("The Survey"), 1915 December 18 (Box 1)